[♪ somber music playing]
[LEON] The war had ended.
Peace between the kingdom
and principality
was established.
Holfort's attention
was soon turned elsewhere.
Nations took advantage
of the situation
by invading,
and they were dealt with.
As for the principality,
it was no more.
House Fanoss
rejoined the kingdom as a duchy.
On top of
the exorbitant reparations
that were demanded
for their actions,
the kingdom was also pushing
for an unfair
and humiliating treaty.
-Queen Mylene.
-Mm?
-[women sigh dreamily]
-[Leon laughing]
Meanwhile, I was in high spirits
from all the attention!
[gasps]
[MYLENE] Viscount Bartfort!
Help me.
I have a request.
Uh...
Whatever it is,
there's no bowing required.
Just go ahead and ask.
Save him.
Please spare Julius
and his friends.
Say what?
You're in jail?
Somehow I'm not surprised.
THIS WORLD
IS REALLY TOUGH FOR MOBS
[JULIUS]
We don't need your help.
[all groan softly]
Speak for yourself!
I'll take their help!
I don't wanna be executed!
Get me out! [crying]
Stop your whining.
If you wanna blame anyone,
blame this idiot
for insulting House Fanoss.
I caused a little commotion,
nothing more.
I merely said
I wouldn't marry Hertrude.
It was being done
to push an unfair treaty
on the principality.
[Marie continues crying]
[JULIUS] I refuse
to be anyone's pawn!
And because of your integrity,
the palace completely lost face.
Look, they were forced
to compromise
heavily on the treaty.
What did you think
was gonna happen?
[HERTRUDE] Unreal.
I never thought that
idiot prince would be my savior.
[LEON] Not to mention you four
went crazy at the temple.
Only because we were trying
to stop Marie's execution!
You might believe she's a fraud,
but she's still our Saint!
We'll never regret
defending her!
We're ready to live
and die for Marie's sake!
You're dead, all right.
You've managed to make enemies
of both the palace
and the temple.
Accept your deaths.
What? No!
I'm too cute to be executed!
[sighs]
Have you lost your mind?
You want to exchange everything
you earned in the war
for their lives?
[LEON] Yes, sir.
And if that's not enough,
then I'll pay
out of my own coffers.
Will you spare them, sire?
Hmm. This is not an easy choice.
[LEON] Okay, bastard!
Milk it for all its worth!
[♪ gentle music playing]
I must ask,
why would you do this for them?
[LEON] Our fates seem
to be inexplicably intertwined.
It's better this way.
My goal was to live
a relaxed life,
not to keep climbing the ranks.
This way,
maybe I can start over.
[chuckles softly]
In that case,
they should consider
themselves lucky
to have such a good friend.
Your Majesty.
If it's all right with you,
I would be happy
to take it from here.
[ROLAND] Hmm?
Hmm.
Yes, very well.
[LEON] Hell to the yeah!
I basically talked my way
to an early retirement!
Lazy mob life, here I come!
There's one more thing.
A matter concerning Angelica.
[LEON] Hmm?
-[JULIUS] Don't do it, Bartfort!
-[all straining]
Are you trying to end up
in here with the rest of us?
[growls] Let me at her!
Marie! Your blood
will stain Murasamekai!
First, where do you keep
getting all these rare items?
Second,
I thought you were saving me!
[LEON] That was before
I heard you made
-Angie and Livia kiss your feet!
-[gasps]
[gasps] I didn't mean to.
Well, I did, but I...
Angie is in disgrace
since you made her tarnish
her family's name!
Do you know how much
you've hurt her and Livia?!
I have no choice but to kill you
and restore their honor!
[gasps]
Fat chance!
If you want to harm Marie,
you'll have to go through us!
[LEON] Luxion,
you know what to do!
[LUXION] If you say so.
[LEON] 100%!
[LUXION] In that case,
one moment please.
[electricity crackling]
[all screaming]
[LEON] Why'd you zap me too?
[LUXION] Now,
has everyone calmed down?
[MARIE] We have to stay
on a floating island?
-In your territory?
-[LEON] Yup.
It has everything you need
to live a self-sufficient life.
Basically, you're being exiled.
Yeah. I'm gonna
have to pass, but thanks.
Considering your crimes,
it's the best offer
you're gonna get!
Unless you'd prefer to,
you know, die.
Well, go back to the table
and get a better deal.
I'm a city girl
through and through.
You just want to stay
so you can build
another harem for yourself!
Try acting like the grown-up
you are for once!
You're one to talk!
Stringing along the villainess
and the protagonist
like some kinda player.
Our relationship is 1,000% pure,
thank you!
We're not like you!
It's not my fault
you're such a wimp!
It is your fault
I ended up here, though!
Luxion! Say something!
[LUXION] Certainly.
I have endless sympathy
for the unfortunate parents
who had you two as children.
[both gasp]
[both whimper]
[LUXION] Also, Marie is correct.
The time has come for you
to make a decision, Master.
[groans] What? Be specific.
[LUXION] I am sure your visitors
-will make it clear.
-[LEON] Huh?
-Leon.
-Good, you're here.
[both whimper]
We need to have a talk.
And I'm afraid it can't wait.
[LEON] So, what did you want
to chat about outside?
Leon.
You should know I love you.
[gasps]
[♪ gentle music playing]
I'm not sure when,
but at some point,
I started thinking about you
more than His Highness
and looking forward
to the time we spent together.
I felt relaxed around you,
like I could be myself.
Eventually,
I realized it was love.
[gasps]
[LEON] Why's she smiling?
Whatever the reason,
it can't be good!
[gasps] We're bros! Help me out!
Hold up! Who are you?!
[CLEARE] It's Cleare!
We've met before.
Wait.
You're the voice of Vice's AI.
[CLEARE] Hello again!
[LEON] Huh.
But before that,
back at the elven ruins,
you were the one
running the lab!
[Cleare giggles]
Until my transfer
to this device.
I wasn't told.
Hey!
Where'd that jerk run off to?
[CLEARE] I asked the professor
to take a back seat.
He was more than happy
to oblige.
Yeah, bet he was more
than happy to abandon me.
-[OLIVIA] Mr. Leon.
-[LEON] Hmm? Livia?
I don't think I need to tell you
how much I love you.
I don't believe
anyone's feelings
are stronger than mine.
Right. Goga!
What the hell am I saying?
We've both been patient,
but you do owe us an answer.
Choose me or Livia.
No, we're not even going to
force you to go that far.
All we ask is you tell us
how you feel.
-[gasps]
-[heart thumping]
How I feel? The truth is...
Here it goes.
[takes deep breath]
I love both of you! [echoing]
[both chuckle softly]
-[slaps]
-[Leon yells]
My dad was promoted
to upper sixth rank
for saving so many evacuees.
He's currently helping me repair
Arroganz and the Partner.
Speaking of partners,
remember his ex, Zola?
Her mansion burned down
during the war.
She got her wish and avoided
her son being conscripted.
All it cost was her title.
Back in the capital,
the balance of power
between the genders
was beginning to equalize.
And then there's me.
[ROLAND]
Viscount Leon Fou Bartfort,
by all accounts,
you performed splendidly
in the war.
[Leon grumbles]
Just get on with it.
[ROLAND] Hmm.
Now that it is over,
I shall relieve you
of your duties
as supreme commander.
And instead, I'm promoting you
to the rank
of count, lower third,
as you so richly deserve.
Huh?
-A count?
-Oh, my word.
[LEON] What about our deal?!
[ROLAND] Given your
numerous achievements in battle,
how could I not grant
such a hero of the kingdom
a suitable title?
[chuckles smugly]
That rank
at his age is unheard of.
That's the highest title
for non-royals.
[MAN] This egoist
will be out of control.
-[gasps]
-[hushed chatter]
[LEON]
Everyone else is shocked too.
You asshole!
You did this to spite me!
You're the game's real villain!
[Roland chuckles]
This is what you get
for trying to outshine the king.
Your wish is my command,
Your Majesty.
[ROLAND] Surrendering
center stage without a fight.
Oh, and I'm looking forward
to your future exploits.
[chuckles smugly]
-[Leon huffs]
-[Roland laughing]
[LEON] Keep grinning,
you sadistic jerk!
One day, I'm gonna
get you back good
and wipe that smile
off your face!
[MARIE] You were promoted again.
Congratulations
on your achievement.
I mean that
with total sincerity.
You might like being
an attention sponge,
but I don't!
While I'm here,
what do you want?
I thought you might like to have
some important information
regarding your favorite
-otome game.
-What?
[MARIE] You'd have no way
of knowing since you died
after beating the first game,
but more titles were announced,
and it eventually
became a series.
No way! That shit has sequels?!
Shocking, right?
Despite it not being popular,
seems the devs were weirdly
passionate about the world.
They should've stopped at one.
[MARIE]
Remember the land guardian?
That was the final boss
of the first game.
And the sky
and sea guardians appear
in the third game.
If that's the case,
then the first and third games
ended up being blended together.
That's why I didn't recognize
the other two. [gasps]
I'm almost scared to ask,
but does that mean--
[MARIE] Bingo!
There's still the boss
from the second game
to deal with.
This world's not
out of danger yet.
[LEON] Gimme a break!
Oh, how the tables have turned.
Looks like I'm the one who knows
the ins and outs
of the game this time.
So, how about you and I
strike a deal?
You beast! What is it you want?
Well, for starters,
since you asked...
[chuckles]
Please give me an allowance!
Huh?
Carla and Kyle will be fine,
but those prettiots could never
survive in the boonies!
-[♪ pop music playing]
-[men laughing]
[MARIE] What did I do
to deserve this?
They're as useless
as the hobosexuals
in my previous life!
[JULIUS] Sparkle! [echoing]
You've got a real talent
for attracting
the most shit guys.
Fine. You can have an allowance.
[gasps] Thanks!
You're the most thoughtful,
selfish, big brother ever!
I agreed to the deal,
so back off and tell me
about the second game.
'Kay.
It doesn't take place here.
The devs changed the location
to the Alzer Republic.
Why does that ring a bell?
[♪ mysterious music playing]
That's right, from the poster.
Apparently,
the world is destroyed
unless the protagonist
gets together
with a romantic interest.
Couldn't they have come up
with a different storyline?
[LUXION] You are the definition
of a worrywart.
Going to the Alzer Republic
as a precaution seems extreme.
Please, like I had a choice.
Imagine if there's
someone like Marie
causing trouble over there.
Besides, I'm curious
how changing the first game
affected things.
[LUXION] If you stayed
in the kingdom,
you would be quite popular.
[LEON] Don't remind me.
Just how tough
is this world for mobs?
[BALCUS] Leon.
-[LEON] What's up, old man?
-Got a second?
-An engagement party?
-How 'bout it?
I was kind of hoping
you'd be able
to make an appearance.
You know, I gotta say,
I way underestimated Nicks.
I didn't think
he'd find a girl so soon.
Yeah,
crazy how these things happen.
I might have time
before studying abroad.
Just kidding,
of course I'll be there!
[♪ lively music playing]
Wait a minute.
Something doesn't
feel right here.
Isn't this your shindig, bro?
So how come I've got
the flashy outfit?
About that.
Right! It's because
you're a count!
What?
Luxion.
Doesn't all this
seem strange to you?
[LUXION]
You are imagining things.
Everyone is just nervous.
[LEON] No,
something's definitely off.
Wait. Don't tell me.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
[gasps]
The hell?! You tricked me!
Uh, I wouldn't
call it a trick actually.
More of a deliberate
misrepresentation.
[LUXION] Since indecision
is your strong suit,
we took the initiative
and made arrangements
on your behalf.
No. How could you do this to me?
Crap! The room's full
of all the bigwigs!
I can't run away!
-[GILBERT] Congratulations.
-[gasps]
Milord,
a letter from His Majesty.
What? From the king?
I understand you've been running
from marriage,
so I've done everything
in my power
to expedite the process for you.
[Leon gasps]
[ROLAND] Welcome
to the beginning
of the end of your life.
Sincerely, your ever-wonderful,
talented king.
-[huffs] Damn it all!
-[Roland laughs]
[whining]
[ANGELICA] We're sorry
for ambushing you like this.
But we all know
you would've kept
dodging the question
if we hadn't.
That's true.
But you guys could have anyone.
Why choose me?
Because you're you, Leon.
So, are you going
to be my husband?
[gasps]
She said it best.
There is no one else like you.
[gasps]
[OLIVIA] I'll never let you go.
[giggling]
Well, I guess if you say so.
[church bell chiming]
[crowd clapping]
[LEON] I mean,
it's not like I don't like them.
In fact, I love them.
As far as ambushes go,
this one doesn't suck.
[LUXION] Congratulations
on your engagement.
[CLEARE] What a truly
wonderful ceremony!
How about an apology
for keeping me in the dark,
you sadistic spheres?
[grumbles] I leave
for the Republic tomorrow.
Feels crappy to bail so soon
after the engagement.
-[knock on door]
-Uh.
[Angelica chuckles softly]
[screams]
I don't know if I'm ready
for this yet!
Peek.
-It feels like it’s too soon!
-You can relax for now, Leon.
We were hoping the three of us
could have a conversation.
-[LEON] Peek?
-We haven't had a chance
to talk much
with everything going on lately.
-Let's fix that.
-[LEON] Right!
[sputtering] That’s what
I thought! Totally fine!
[♪ gentle music playing]
We wanted to say we're grateful.
Since the day we met you,
it feels like our lives
have completely changed.
And no matter what,
you were always there
by our sides.
You've helped us out so much.
-[chuckles softly]
-[LEON] Angie, Livia.
I owe you guys.
Without you in my life,
I don't think I would
have made it this far.
And I guess the same goes
for Marie and her morons.
They do mean well.
Leon, you'd better come back.
We'll both be here
waiting for you.
[chuckles softly]
I will. I promise.
-[laughing]
-[LEON] Afterwards,
we stayed up
the entire night...
[laughing]
...just talking.
Trust me,
it was absolute torture.
[trees rustling]
Rauda...
everybody's gone now.
First our father and mother,
then you, and even Vandel.
[♪ somber music playing]
It feels like
you're still with me.
Maybe it's just because
I don't wanna be alone.
If only I'd been stronger,
things would've
turned out differently.
For some reason, I'm reminded
of the elf chief's words.
And of him, Leon Fou Bartfort.
[PRIESTESS] If you're somehow
able to find
a way to walk together,
this path of thorns
will instead be bathed in light.
They shall be a reliable source
of support for you.
♪
[RAYMOND] I can't believe
you're leaving.
Man, you couldn't have picked
a worse time for it.
Right when you started to have
some luck with the ladies.
We're being treated like heroes
for our evacuation efforts,
so we can't complain.
[BOTH] We're entering
our popular phase!
Keep this up,
it'll be short-lived.
-[CLARICE] You can't leave yet.
-[gasps]
[LEON] Oh. Afternoon, you two.
If you get tired
of the Redgraves, don't forget.
House Atlee's here for you.
-[gasps]
-It goes without saying,
but House Roseblade's doors
are always open.
What if we just
pulled the trigger?
Indeed, we could
run away and elope.
[laughs]
[LUCAS] Mr. Leon.
[LEON] Master!
I believe seeing
the outside world
will help you grow,
both as a noble and a man.
May you continue
to deepen your code of chivalry
-as you push forward.
-I will, sir!
[LUXION] Pardon,
but it is nearly time to depart.
I have procured a new ship
so you will not
embarrass yourself
as a representative
of the kingdom.
Nice! [laughs]
[LUXION]
It is called the Einhorn.
I felt it worthy
of today's departure.
Let's take this beaut
for a scoot.
[CLEARE] I am confused.
Why were you not there
for his departure?
Imagine, the trouble
we would have caused him.
I guarantee
there would have been tears.
[CLEARE] I see! How admirable!
[ANGELICA]
There must be a good reason
why he suddenly decided
to study abroad.
We plan to study hard ourselves
so we can better help him
when he comes back!
Let's make a pact that
when Leon finally returns home,
he'll be amazed
by how much we've grown!
[ANGELICA] We'll do our best!
-[OLIVIA] Just like Leon!
-[both chuckle]
It's not fair!
After that lovely send-off,
who'd wanna go
on this stupid trip?!
-[thudding]
-[crying]
[LUXION] It is wise
to get your tantrum
out of the way before we land.
Also...
are you going
to open this mystery box?
Apparently, it was brought
aboard from the palace.
Well, that might
distract me at least.
Maybe it's the royals' gift
to the Republic?
[groans softly]
You did not just
close the lid on me!
Would you prefer that
I throw the box overboard?!
[both panting heavily]
I... I can explain.
[♪ closing theme song playing]
What the heck is that?
A humble monument
in honor of our Saint.
It took a while to find
a worthy craftsman.
You can rest assured
we spared no expense.
Our allowance
from Bartfort was barely enough
to cover the cost.
The artist tried
making your chest bigger,
but we wanted realism.
Gone, just like that.
An entire fortune
down the drain.
It was supposed
to last us a year.
We're screwed.
[whimpers]
[MARIE] These lovesick airheads
are driving me crazy!
[thunderclap]
The queen was furious
when she found out.
[whimpering]
You were given a second chance,
and this is how you repay
those who stuck
their necks out for you?
[growls]
Your punishment will be
to study abroad with Leon!
[sighs]
You probably guessed,
but the rest of them
are here too.
[JILK] Exciting, isn't it,
Your Highness?
-[JULIUS] Indeed.
-[CHRIS] Alzer, huh?
[BRAD] I'll be happy anywhere
if Marie is there!
[GREG] One day, I'll become
a man worthy of her.
[JULIUS] Brand new adventure.
Brand new boys!
[ALL] Yeah! [laugh]
Isn't it awesome?
We're gonna spend
lots of time together!
You won't have
to be alone, brother.
[LEON] This is 100 times worse!
[LUXION] This must be that
beautiful bond between siblings
I have heard so much about.
You certainly look related
when you make that face.
[both growl] Shut up, droid!
[LEON] I can't win!
Damn this shitty otome game!
This world
really is tough for mobs!
TRAPPED IN A DATING SIM 2
SUPREME COMMANDER
MIURA KAZUYA